
export const quizData = [
    { question: "1. Which planet is closest to the Sun?", options: ["Venus", "Mercury", "Earth", "Mars"], answer: "Mercury", type: "mcq" },
    { question: "2. Which data structure follows FIFO?", options: ["Stack", "Queue", "Tree", "Graph"], answer: "Queue", type: "mcq" },
    { question: "3. Which of the following is primarily used for structuring web pages?", options: ["Python", "Java", "HTML", "C++"], answer: "HTML", type: "mcq" },
    { question: "4. Which chemical symbol stands for Gold?", options: ["Au", "Gd", "Pt", "Ag"], answer: "Au", type: "mcq" },
    { question: "5. Which of these processes is not typically involved in refining petroleum?", options: ["Fractional distillation", " Cracking", "Filtration", "Polymerization"], answer: "Fractional distillation", type: "mcq" },
    { question: "6. What is 12 + 28?", answer: 40, type: "integer" },
    { question: "7. How many states are there in the United States?", answer: 50, type: "integer" },
    { question: "8. In which year was the Declaration of Independence signed?", answer: 1947, type: "integer" },
    { question: "9. What is the value of pi rounded to the nearest integer?", answer: 3, type: "integer" },
    { question: "10. If a car travels at 60 mph for 2 hours, how many miles does it travel?", answer: 120, type: "integer" },
  ];
  